Angel of Death is going to breakfast
today the ribs sucked to tattoo black
and grade isn't my strong suit
this sounds like a nightmare from those
start to finish how do you want to do it
apocalypse angel he has staff standing
by our tombstone what to crow there with
his hand out do you want to do like a
full body type of thing yeah I'm at the
mercy of this goal who will not budge on
his idea do you feel comfortable just
doing him nah I needed to look like this
apocalyptic in the background you know
no background behind it that's a lot to
cram into a six-hour tattoo on the ribs
you know there's no way I'm gonna be
been able to pull this off
[Music]
to finish it
great tattooers go home all the time on
this competition because you're at the
mercy of your campus and this dude is
doc I think I'm go home don't plan your
funeral before your body dies even if he
was being a Kyle is still my little
brother and I love him but I want him to
do well it's so difficult knowing that I
can't do anything to help him out
[Music]
Jason Hey look out fires wow it's so
yeah thanks Roley
[Music]
first thing on the ribs we have to go
smaller and it's gonna be less detail
because it takes a lot longer to tattoo
it on the ribs so I want to switch it
off the ribs
I mean I'd really want the ribs just
because my legs are water and my torsos
hair the more likely we can change the
location the bigger cooler is how to use
I'm not gonna tap out or anything like
that I have a full back PE sternum I
could be really screwed right now I mean
if this girl makes the slightest
movement my lines are gonna play and
that will send me home I'm super happy
that Steve's team is in trouble because
I'm pissed at Rowley right now and give
me the rib tattoo he's in the tricky
spot when you put a design on the ribs
and then they lay down it gets really
big so you're having to do twice the
amount of work I wanted to go detailed
but it's on the ribs so I think it's
better to make sure we get a tattoo done
and it's clean Jason your color looks
punched you're the first one so far that
has a waxy glow to your tattoo the
placement is what kills this thing the
balloon is so slender and straight and
the basket is directly underneath it and
it's just turned on its side it just
doesn't look like a hot-air balloon
it looks like a chalice of blood with
butterflies flying out of it
where's anymore
black anchor they gave us the biggest
piece it's like what's up Aaron and doom
I thought you guys are back volcano huh
because you are you open to moving there
you pretty some with the ribs you can
you just take off your shirt first
I'm nervous about him sitting for six
hours on his ribs he wants a big he
wants it pulled it's a lot of saturation
did you see Carlos immerse yeah
massive what they do all day there every
day like hanker is a world-class job and
it is known the world over for having
really great realism artists how you
guys doing about the jam on it I'm
confused at this point that I am even in
an alliance in this competition I think
they gave us that harder one maybe to
try and knock us down a little bit I'm
fighting that lip pop right now honestly
I feel like we could really shine I just
hope that time is on our side
you got that lava flow we've got a big
piece of it crank it out man pedal to
the metal guys we expect a lot out of
American Carlos just cuz we know where
they come from
black anchor collective is already a
very well-known very established shop in
the country
black anchor struggling none of the
details they have so far finished all
that wavy ground it's sketchy I just
don't think that they're prepared to do
a tattoo that can be finished in six
hours they don't do it at home and I
don't think they're gonna be able to do
it here black anchor the perimeter shape
is just an obtrusive big smear on the
side of his body you got to leave some
open skin it's like everywhere you look
in this tattoo is a cover-up
the only contrast you have is from the
areas of solid color to the areas of
light color he did as far as details go
there's no detail this is one of the
rougher tattoos I've seen here guy once
battling each other
Mike I got this crazy bother
who wants a space battle on his side
this is a nightmare so I wanted like a
whole battlefield and then with the
planet a black hole or wormhole
whichever had some kind of alien
battlefield like are they battling on a
planet no there's just in outer space
shooting at it yeah pretty much you know
flying saucers you okay you've gotta be
kidding me
the tattoo that I'm gonna make will
probably be around this size but it'll
be easy to build off of because we won't
finish if you do your hosts ribs I think
it should be able to totally should be
able to it's not possible to finish
something that size if I don't finish
this tattoo I am screwed
[Music]
this canvas keeps moving around he is
not sitting very well at all sir Mike's
tuned into outer space right now with
his canvas
I think I'm really like you've hit
contrasts here there is some nice areas
of darkness in the space but you've got
circles you got different areas that are
geometrically supposed to be parallel
and perfect and they're all a little
rough that dude was weird
he just kept sitting up and moving all
around and he wouldn't sit still what I
don't like is a way you tattooed it
doesn't have that finished look that I'm
used to seeing from you it doesn't have
the Polish this is why you don't want to
phone those flash challenges in no
you're gonna get a guy like this if you
do if I get a skull pick my ghetto
[Music]
dragon coming out of my ribcage ripping
out of the stand and putting inside out
like yep and you're not moving it from
your ribs nope
[Music]
I'm not moving it this canvases ideas
are nuts if this is what he thinks
traditional Japanese dragons are he's
loony sausage I'm just wondering what
sausage did to them guys oh lord have
mercy what will be smoothly won't be bad
like things but it ain't coming off the
ribs okay at laugh-in Sergey had lap
band surgery I had it done I lost over
200 pounds can I take a look at your
ribs
holy crap a lot of loose skin the
swelling of the skin is gonna be
immediate when people lose a lot of
weight their skin becomes very rubbery
it's like thin paper you can blow a line
just by whispering the biggest thing
that I have going against me is your
skin of course you got to overcome adapt
baby she thought it was oh this is the
skins bad because I lost the weight yeah
totally it's been stretched out I got
the worst canvas of the day because the
skin is so fragile if I'm not careful
it's gonna swell up to the point where I
can't tattoo it all right
burn so good
it's not very fun Oh Christian and clean
were clearly out to screw me on the
threat they're trying to take me out
I appreciate you fighting through with
this how you doing buddy starting to get
a little rough let it burn let me
straight man sausage is totally rattled
I almost feel guilty
almost I'm pretty sure so I'm just going
to eat my face tonight so he's beyond a
good sausage should be feeling like a
little kid because he's gonna get
spanked today let's take this last stab
at it okay my canvas is really feeling
the pain he's kind of jostling around in
the chair this is not making it easy for
me to do these really smooth blends that
I need to nail I'm screwed
sausage
the legibility this tattoo is lost just
in the way you shaded it you put black
right up to the edge of the Dragon and
then black right inside the Dragon the
same tones inside the head is there
outside the head it makes it overall
messy
the problem with skin that has weight
loss it's much harder when it's deflated
that being said you do have some Anatomy
issues the neck is so thick and then you
really taper down to this thin body it
makes it seem like the head is way in
the foreground and the rest of the
dragon's way off in the background your
big downfall is the drawing
[Music]